<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WikiAudio</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_screen">MainScreenActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="no_wikipage_title">Click on a wikipage to play it!</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="dialog_record_intro">

             <big><b>There are great tips and guide lines to help you make a
                 great recording</b></big>\n\n

            would you like to see them now?  \n\n

    </string>
    <string name="tips_button">Show me tips and guid lines!</string>
    <string name="false_button">Im ready to record</string>


    <string name="tips_and_guide_lines">
        <big><b>Thank you for wanting to contribute a recording to wikipedia!</b></big>\n\n
        here are a few tips to make a great recording:\n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li>Say the section title before starting to read the section content </li>\n\n
        </font>

        <li /><li>Go over the section before you record it.</li>\n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li>Treat links like text when reading.
            Any vocal indication of every link would disrupt the flow.</li> \n\n
        </font>

        <li /><li>Speak more slowly than normal, by about 25%. You should have about
        150–160 words per minute so people can comfortably hear an article.
            The most conversational speech is at 200 words per minute or more.</li>\n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li>Warm up. The vagaries of the day can leave your vocal cords clogged, especially if you
        have recently been eating or drinking milk-based foods such as cheese and chocolate.
        Some gentle humming before starting to record can cleanse and moisten the vocal cords
            leading to a better sound to the voice. </li>\n\n
        </font>

        <li /><li>Stay relaxed. Whenever you realize that your voice is becoming tenser than normal,
        or you are having more and more trouble speaking fluently, take a break, and resume when you
            feel muscular tension going away.</li> \n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li>Keep some fresh (not cold) water in reach, and drink some whenever you feel your
            mouth drying out. </li> \n\n
        </font>

        <li /><li>Speak outward, with your chin up. Posture and facial expressions can affect voice
            recordings.</li> \n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li> Record at a quiet place to reduce noise. </li> \n\n
        </font>

        <li /><li>Try standing up. If you think your voice sounds a little thin or lacking in
            expression, standing while recording might help. Radio announcers and actors
            regularly stand while speaking to lend additional depth and confidence to their
            performance.</li> \n\n

        <font color="#85b4ff">
        <li /><li> Speak across the microphone or to the side of it, rather than directly into it,
        to avoid pops and breath noise. A distance of several centimeters or inches away from
            the microphone is recommended.</li> \n\n
        </font>
    </string>
    <string name="dont_show_tips">im ready to record</string>

    <string name="why_participate">
        <big> <b>Why participate? </b></big>\n\n
        Here are just some reasons why it is worthwhile creating spoken recordings of articles.
        <li> Spoken articles make Wikipedia content available to those who can understand English but cannot
            read it. </li> \n\n
        <li> Users can listen to Wikipedia articles while they perform tasks that preclude reading but not
            concentration (such as running, or housework). </li> \n\n
        <li> Visually impaired users can use screen readers, but they may not be as
            accurate as a human </li> \n\n
        <li> Vocal performance. This is a valuable learning tool for those learning English.
            If a link is given to the version of the page that was recorded then users may listen
        to the words while reading them.</li> \n\n
        <li> They are a valuable learning tool for auditory learners (people who learn most
            effectively by listening to information delivered orally). </li> \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="license_string">
        This sound file and all text in the article are licensed under the Creative Commons
        Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported License, available at creative commons dot org slash
        licenses slash by hyphen S A slash three point zero."
    </string>
    <string name="section_dialog_title">Sections:</string>

    <string name="license_data">
        This file will be uploaded under the following license: \n\n
        This file is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike
        3.0 Unported license. \n\n
        People are free:\n
        to share – to copy, distribute and transmit the work, to remix – to adapt the work,
        Under the following conditions:\n\n
        attribution – You must give appropriate credit.\n\n
        provide a link to the license, and indicate if changes were made. You may do so in any
        reasonable manner, but not in any way that suggests the licensor endorses you or your
        use.\n\n
        share alike – If you remix, transform, or build
        upon the material, you must distribute your contributions
        under the same or compatible license as the original.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="upload_dialog_title">Uploading File</string>
</resources>
